http://www.thefttalk.com/privacy_policy.html

FAQ
Is this class right for you?
Theft Tips
Is Time Really Money?
An 4 or 8 hour
Theft / Shoplifting class that you can stop and start anytime you want - on your schedule! This
Theft / Shoplifting class is completely self-paced, sign out and come back later, the computer will take you back to where you ended. That's right, work on it a half hour at a time, more sometimes, less others - you choose.
Less Expensive: One fee, no added fees. Our online
Theft / Shoplifting class sets an industry standard as one of the nation's premier provider of online
Theft / Shoplifting classes. A 4 or 8 hour
Theft / Shoplifting class or ourTheft / Shoplifting workbook.
Privacy Policy
When you contact Theft Talk™ or when you register for services from Theft Talk™, we may ask you to provide personal information. Theft Talk™ uses the information collected from you to provide services to you or to solicit information from you regarding the quality of services we provided or outcomes for the services we provided. TTOS.us™ does NOT sell, rent, or lease our customer list to third parties. Our privacy policy is strict; a) when an agency/referral source notifies TTOS.us™ that a person/client is required to complete an TTOS.us™ online class or workbook class, upon the request of the agency/referral source or the client, TTOS.us™ will notify said agency/referral source of the client's completion status and other relevant information. b) when a client elects to use an TTOS.us™ online class, TTOS.us™ will not initiate notice to others (i.e., judges, probation officers, parents, school authorities) of the client's participation in our services or provide completion status documentation without the express permission from the client, however, c) when requested by a verified referral source, TTOS.us™ will provide progress updates, including completion status regardless if participation in the TTOS.us™ class was by referral or elected by the client. TTOS.us™, under most circumstances will provide any and all information demanded by a legally issued subpoena.. TTOS.us™ reserves the right to update and change these policies at any time, with or without your notice. It is your responsibility to periodically review the TTOS.us™ privacy policy. This is the official notice of the TTOS.us™ Privacy Policy and, as such, this notice shall take precedence over any other TTOS.us™ Privacy Policy notice.
A Really Good Choice
Our
Theft / Shoplifting class is a convenient way to complete a court ordered, PO, diversion or school required program.
You can take the class from any
location in the United States, Europe, Canada or Australia with a computer and internet access.
There is nothing to download or print, simply register, log in, pay and begin your
class.
Privacy | Professionals
Is Our Theft Class Right for You?
Theft Related Laws in Your State
Our Courses Include:
24 hour access to your class
Immediate Proof of Enrollment
Nothing to download
Start and stop at any time - work at your pace on your timelines
Use home computer or public library
A world class learning experience
User friendly
Support by phone weekdays, by email 7 days a week
Free Certificate of Completion immediately available upon completion
Our Philosophy
Change your thoughts and you change your world .
~Norman Vincent Peale
(1898 - 1993)
Copyright © 2005~2020-21 TheftTalk.com by TT Online Services
Privacy Information | Contact | Links | Site Map
